History is catching up with them.
Mr. Peabody & Sherman is a animation, science fiction,
comedy film directed by Rob Minkoff.
A young boy and his dog, who happens to have a genius-level IQ, spring into action when
their time-machine is stolen and moments in history begin to be changed.
Mr. Peabody (voice), played by Ty Burrell.
Sherman (voice), played by Max Charles.
Penny Peterson (voice), played by Ariel Winter.
Ms. Grunion (voice), played by Allison Janney.
Paul Peterson (voice), played by Stephen Colbert.
Principal Purdy (voice), played by Stephen Tobolowsky.
Peabody & Sherman is a 2014 American animated science fiction
comedy film produced by DreamWorks Animation.
The film is based on characters from the "Peabody's Improbable History"
segments of the animated television series Rocky & Friends.
It was directed by Rob Minkoff and written by Craig Wright.
It features the voices of Ty Burrell, Max Charles, Ariel Winter,
Stephen Colbert, Leslie Mann, and Allison Janney.
In the film, Mr.
Peabody and his adoptive human son Sherman use the WABAC, a time
machine, to embark on time travel adventures.
When Sherman accidentally rips a hole in the universe by taking the WABAC without permission to impress his
classmate Penny Peterson, they must find themselves to repair history and save the future.
The film was originally planned as a live-action/CG film until it was redeveloped into a fully
computer-animated film in 2006 when Minkoff joined DreamWorks Animation to direct an adaptation.
Andrew Kurtzman was initially set to write the screenplay, based on a pitch
by Minkoff and his longtime producing partner Jason Clark.
Peabody & Sherman was released theatrically in the
United States on March 7, 2014.
Despite grossing $275 million worldwide against a budget of $145
million, the film underperformed by DreamWorks' standards.
Along with Penguins of Madagascar later that year,
it lost the studio $57 million.
It was followed by a TV series, The Mr.
Peabody & Sherman Show, in 2015.
The film explores themes of friendship, egypt, parent
child relationship, intelligence, adoption.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.